<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Meine Mediathek</string>
    <string name="btn_search">Search</string>
    <string name="not_title_download_of_movie">Downloading %s</string>
    <string name="not_desc_download_of_movie">Downloading movie. Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="btn_download_movie">Download movie</string>
    <string name="tv_movie_title">Title:</string>
    <string name="tv_movie_description">Description:</string>
    <string name="et_hint_searchfortitle">Search for movie title</string>
    <string name="btn_agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="btn_disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="btn_cancel_download">Cancel download</string>
    <string name="dlg_title_download_on_mobile">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="dlg_msg_download_on_mobile">You are currently not using a WiFi connection. When downloading using a cellular connection high costs may be charged by your provider.\n\nDo you really want to download this file using a cellular connection?</string>
    <string name="dlg_title_license">License</string>
    <string name="dlg_msg_license">This application was developed to support people watching their favorite  movies from the ZDF Mediathek while they have no internet access. It was NOT developed to download copy protected material and it is not intended to do so.\n\nThe content is provided by a third-party and you have to fulfill their license to be allowed to download their content.\n\nIf you agree to use this app without trying to violate someone\'s rights you are free to use it, otherwise go back to the Google Play Store and uninstall this app.</string>
    <string name="dlg_title_timeout">Timeout</string>
    <string name="dlg_msg_timeout">There was a request time out while fetching information from the content provider. Most of the time it will work if you go back and try it again.</string>
    <string name="dlg_title_appcrash">The app crashed</string>
    <string name="dlg_msg_appcrash">Sorry, but it seems that there is a bug in the application which caused it to crash right now. Please help me fix this bug as soon as possible by sending me a crash report which (hopefully) helps me to locate the bug.\n\nWould you like to send me a bug report (via email)?</string>

</resources>